Guide to the Cornell University News Service records, [ca. 1920s-2000s].
Cornell University News Service records
- Series VI. Cornell University News Services records, 1920s-2000s
  - Subseries VIb. Photographs
    - Buildings (Interior and Exterior)
      - North Campus Dorms, 1969-1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 67a, Folder 59)
      - North Campus Dorms, 1969-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 67a, Folder 60)
      - Noyes Center, 1967-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 67a, Folder 61)
      - Noyes Center, 1970-1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 67a, Folder 62)
      - Noyes Center, 1976-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 67a, Folder 63)
      - Nuclear Reactor Facility, sketch of proposed design (vitro Engineering Co.), construction, exterior and interior, 1959-1961 (Box 4-3-15 - 67a, Folder 64)
      - Olin Hall, 1989 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 1)
      - Olin Library, 1959-1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 2)
      - Olin Library, 1966-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 3)
      - Olin Library, 1968-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 4)
      - Olin Library, 1976-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 5)
      - Olin Library, 1978-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 6)
      - Olin Library (Kroch Extension), 1991 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 7)
      - NSF Awards/Trustees at Olin Library, 10/13/88; 0113 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Ithaca Centennial Exhibit at Olin Library, 12/09/88; 0162 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Ornithology Lab, 1968-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 8)
      - Patrick Gill at Performing Arts Center, 10/4/88; 0111 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Trustees at Performing Arts Center, 10/14/88; 0105 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Performing Arts Center, 11/29/88; 0156 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Performing Arts Center Ballet Class, 11/29/88; 0157 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Performing Arts Center, 11/29/88; 0158 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Performing Arts Center, 11/29/88; 0159 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Performing Arts Center, 11/29/88; 0160 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Cascadilla Trail / Performing Arts Center Exteriors, 1/30/89; 0195 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Performing Arts Center lobby, exterior, 2/7/89; 0201 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Rand Hall (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 9)
      - Residence Life, 1976-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 10)
      - Robert Purcell Union - Interiors, 1971-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 11)
      - Rockefeller Hall, 1969, 1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 12)
      - Rockefeller Hall, 1978-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 13)
      - Rockefeller Hall - Interiors, 1971-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 14)
      - Rockefeller Hall - Interiors, 1977-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 15)
      - Sage Chapel, 1959-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 16)
      - Sage Chapel, 1975-1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 17)
      - Sage Chapel, 1982-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 18)
      - Sage Chapel - Interiors, 1966 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 19)
      - Sage Chapel - Interiors, 1970-1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 20)
      - Sage Chapel - Miscellaneous, 1990-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 89, Folder 8)
      - Sage Hall, 1965-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 21)
      - Sage Graduate Center, 1966-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 22)
      - Sage Graduate Center, 1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 23)
      - Savage Hall, 1948-1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 24)
      - Savage Hall, 1952 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 25)
      - Schwartz Center for the Performing Arts Groundbreaking, 1984-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 26)
      - Sibley Hall, 1966-1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 27)
      - Sibley Hall, 1982-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 28)
      - Sibley Hall - Exterior, 1973-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 29)
      - Sibley Hall - Interiors, 1967-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 30)
      - Sibley Hall - Interiors, 1976-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 31)
      - Snee Hall Dedication, 1976-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 32)
      - IBM Commercial, Snee Hall, 8/3/88; 0011 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - IBM Commercial, Snee Hall, 8/3/88; 0012 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Space Sciences, exterior, Prof. Siegel and electron microscope, 1967 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 33-34)
      - Space Sciences, 1967-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 35)
      - Space Sciences - Interiors, 1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 36)
      - Sperry Hall Dedication, 1966 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 37)
      - Statler Hall in Construction, 1949-1950 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 38)
      - Model Statler Hotel Room, 8/29/88; 0042 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Statler Auditorium, 9/29/88; 0080 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Statler construction/ANC Conference, 11/19/88; 0147 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Statler Hotel: Amphitheater, 3/15/89; 0257 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Faculty Move into Statler, 8/16/88; 0026 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Statler Hall, 1972-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 39)
      - Statler Hall, 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 40)
      - Statler Hall (Dedication Plaque) (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 41)
      - Stimson Hall, 1975, 1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 42)
      - Stimson Hall, 1982-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 43)
      - Theory Center Groundbreaking, 1 1/3/88; 0126 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Theory Center Groundbreaking, 11/3/88; 0127 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Theory Center Reception/ Creative Mgmt. Course, 11/3/88; 0128 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - copied slides: Homecoming parade/Theory Center Graphic, 11/5/88; 0132 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Copy negs. - Theory Center Plans, 8/22/88; 0036 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Theory Center, Moving in the New Supercomputer, 9/28/88; 0074 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Theory Center, Moving in the New Supercomputer, 9/28/88; 0075 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Theory Center, Hooking up the Supercomputer, 9/29/88; 0077 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Tjaden/Franklin Hall, 1966-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 44)
      - Tjaden/Franklin Hall, 1982-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 45)
      - University Press, 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 46)
      - Upper Campus Buildings, 1969-1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 47)
      - Uris Hall Dedication, 1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 48)
      - Uris Hall and Uris Terrace Dedication (Contact Sheets), October 13, 1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 49)
      - Uris Hall, 1970-1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 50)
      - Uris Hall, 1971-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 51)
      - Uris Hall, 1972-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 52)
      - Uris Hall - Interiors, 1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 53)
      - Uris Hall - Interiors, 1979-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 54)
      - Uris Library, 1959-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 55)
      - Uris Library and McGraw Clocktower, 1966-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 56)
      - Uris Library, 1966-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 57)
      - Uris Library, 1973-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 58)
      - Uris Library, 1975-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 59)
      - Uris Library - Exterior, 1973-1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 60)
      - Uris Library - Addition Dedication, 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 61)
      - Uris Library - Addition, 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 62)
      - Uris Library - Andrew Dickson White Library, 1973-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 63)
      - Uris Library - Andrew Dickson White Library, 1974-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 64)
      - Uris Library - Annex Exterior, 1982-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 65)
      - Various Dedication Ceremonies, 1978-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 66)
      - Veterinary College, 1969-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 67)
      - Veterinary College, 1969-1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 68)
      - Veterinary College - Library and Miscellaneous Facilities, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 69)
      - Veterinary College - Library and Miscellaneous Facilities, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 70)
      - West Campus - Dormitories, 1965-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 71)
      - West Campus - U-Hall Exteriors, 1968-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 72)
      - West Campus - U-Hall Interiors, 1982-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 73)
      - White Hall, 1966-1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 74)
      - Willard Straight Hall, 1965-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 75)
      - Willard Straight Hall, 1966-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 76)
      - Willard Straight Hall, 1968 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 77)
      - Willard Straight Hall, 1968-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 78)
      - Willard Straight Hall - Interiors, 1965-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 79)
      - Willard Straight Hall - Interiors, 1981-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 68, Folder 80)
      - Willard Straight Hall: Interiors, 1968-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 1)
      - Memorial Room/Zhang Xinxin, 12/14/88; 0171 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Women's Dorms (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 2)
    - Classes, Programs, and Student Activities
      - Africana Studies and Research Center, Janheinz Jahn, 1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 3)
      - Africana Studies and Research Center (Contact Sheets), 1973 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 4)
      - Africana Studies and Research Center, 1994-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 5-11)
      - Africana Studies and Research Center - Library, 1969-1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 12)
      - Africana Studies and Research Center (Contact Sheets), 1966-1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 13)
      - Alumni University (Contact Sheets), 1968-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 14)
      - American Indian Program, 1991-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 15)
      - American Indian Program (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 16)
      - Anthropology, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 17)
        Prof. Robert Ascher with Quipu
      - Anthropology Time Capsule (Contact Sheets), 1968 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 18)
      - Architecture, 1950-1962 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 19)
        Model of Grand Bahama Island
        Colorado Shale Oil City Plan
        Model of the future Waikiki Beach
        Solatron (John Vatet, Prof. Edmondson, Robert Matyas)
      - Architecture, 1967 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 20)
      - Architecture, 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 21)
      - Architecture (Contact Sheets), 1966-1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 22)
      - Architecture (Contact Sheets), 1977-1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 23)
      - Architecture - Bird Cages, 1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 24-25)
      - Architecture - New York City Trip, 1967-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 26)
      - Architecture - Tin Can Project, 1967 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 27)
      - Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1970-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 28)
      - Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1991-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 29)
      - Architecture and Fine Arts, 1965-1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 30)
      - Architecture and Fine Arts, 1973-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 31)
      - Architecture and Fine Arts, 1977-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 32)
      - Art Classes (in Tjaden Hall), 1968-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 33)
      - Art Classes (in Tjaden Hall), 1977-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 34)
      - Art Classes - Nudes, 1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 35)
      - Arts, Music and Theatre, 1970-1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 36)
      - Arts, Music and Theatre, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 37)
      - Arts, Music and Theatre, 1975-1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 38)
      - Arts and Sciences, 1993-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 39)
      - Asimolar - Brown/Cornell Weekend Seminar, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 40)
      - Big Red Band, 1970-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 43-44)
      - Big Red Band, 1974-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 41)
      - Big Red Band, 1975-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 43-44)
      - Big Red Band, 1977-1987 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 42)
      - Black Gospel, 1981-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 45)
      - Black Gospel and Theatre Conference, 1971-1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 46)
      - Black Gospel and Theatre Conference, 1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 47)
      - Black Theatre, 1966-1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 48)
      - Bursar's Office, 1971-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 49)
      - School of Business and Public Administration, 1960-1964 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 50)
        1964 - Malott Hall exterior and dedication
        , 1960-Students with Harry Gasarch from Mobil International
        , Misc.-Library in McGraw, classrooms
      - School of Business and Public Administration, 1966-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 69, Folder 51)
      - School of Business and Public Administration (Contact Sheets), 1966-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 1)
      - Business and Public Administration Housing Project, 180 students working in cooperation with the Mayor's Citizen Advisory Committee, 1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 2)
      - Business School Executive Development Program, 1967-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 3)
      - Campus Activities, 1969-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 4)
      - Cayuga's Waiters, 1966 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 5)
      - a: Booksale/Chimes, 11/2/88; 0121 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - b: Chimes, 1 1/2/88; 0122 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Chimes/Cornell Scenics, 11/2/88; 0123 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - David Parker and new chimes practice stunt, 3/3/89; 0240 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Chimes, 1987-1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 6)
      - Student Playing the Chimes, 1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 51)
      - Robert Louis Oakley (Chimesmaster), 1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 22)
      - Chimes, 1966-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 86, Folder 46)
      - China-Japan Program, 1977-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 7)
      - Choral, 1968 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 8)
      - Choral, 1975-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 9)
      - City and Regional Planning (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 10)
      - CLASP (Community Learning and Service Partnership) (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 11)
      - Classrooms/Lectures, 1960-1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 12)
      - College Bowl (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 13)
      - College Production of "The Good Woman of Szechaun", 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 14)
      - Cooperative Extension, 1993-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 15)
        Includes photo of developing the agenda for the first meeting of the National 4-H Club.
      - Cornell Abroad, 1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 16)
      - Cornell Clubs (Miscellaneous), 1987-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 17)
      - Cornell Daily Sun and WVBR, 1973, 1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 18)
      - Cornell Senate, 1970-1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 19)
      - Cornell Senate, 1970-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 20)
      - Cornell Senate, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 21)
      - Cornell in Washington, 1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 22)
      - COSEP (Committee on Special Educational Projects), 1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 23)
        Delridge Hunter, director of COSEP
        Laray Thomona Brown
        F. Eastman
        J. Orduna
        Dr. E. Hart
        Prof. J. Turner
        C. Galvin
        Prof. J. Congress Mioata
        M. Jenkins
        R.P. Bates
        F.G. Washington, A.C. Walker
        E.A. Salter
        F.G. Jones
        K.A. McClane Jr.
        Gabriel Garcia
      - COSEP, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 24-25)
      - CRESP (Center for Religion, Ethics, and Social Policy), 1993-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 26)
      - CURW (Cornell United Religious Work)(, 1993-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 27)
      - Design and Environmental Analysis, 1993-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 28)
      - Drama, 1950s (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 29)
      - Drum Corps, 1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 30)
      - Ecology House, 1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 31)
      - Education, 1954 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 32)
      - Extracurriculars, 1970s (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 33)
        Including singing telegram sale (AEO), student conference in Anabel Taylor, St. Patrick's Party in Catholic office
      - Final Exams, 1966-1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 34)
      - Final Exams, 1970-1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 35)
      - Final Exams, 1971-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 36)
      - Food Science and Marketing, 1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 37)
        Art Maver
        Robert C. Baker
        Bob Gravani
      - Forensics Team, 1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 38)
      - Fraternities and Sororities, 1960-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 39)
      - Fraternities and Sororities, 1992-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 40)
      - Delta Kappa Epsilon Tree/Ryozo Morishita, 2/11/89; 0206 (Box 4-3-15 - 63)
      - Glee Club, 1959-1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 41)
        Possibly includes: In Temple of Zeus With Philadelphia Orchestra (Alumni Week 1965) conductor Eugene Ormandy
      - Glee Club Tour (Contact Sheets), 1966 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 42)
      - Glee Club, 1966-1968 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 43)
      - Glee Club, 1968-1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 44)
      - Glee Club, 1994-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 45)
      - Guest Lecturers - New York State Science and Technology, 1965-1966 (Box 4-3-15 - 73, Folder 37)
        Tricomi
        Jacques Deny
        Mantned Eigen
        Isao Imai
        M. Goldhaber
        Knipling
        Gordon J.F. MacDonald, 1965-1966
      - Hispanic American Studies, 1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 46)
      - Home Economics, 1952-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 47)
      - Home Economics, 1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 48-49)
      - Hotel School, 1950s (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 50)
      - Hotel School, 1960s (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 51)
      - Hotel School, 1960s (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 52)
      - Hotel School, 1969-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 53)
      - Hotel School, 1973-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 54)
      - Hotel School, 1988-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 55)
      - Human Development and Family Studies (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 56)
      - Human Ecology, 1969-1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 57)
      - Human Ecology, 1992-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 58)
      - Human Ecology, 1994-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 59)
      - Industrial and Labor Relations, 1960-1963 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 60)
      - Industrial and Labor Relations (Contact Sheets), 1967-1974 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 61)
      - Industrial and Labor Relations, 1971-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 62)
      - Industrial and Labor Relations, 1992-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 63)
      - Industrial and Labor Relations, 1995-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 70, Folder 64)
      - Jewish Studdies, 1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 1)
      - Johnson Museum, 1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 2)
      - Johnson School, 1988-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 3)
      - Language Lab, 1968 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 4)
      - Latin American Studies Program, 1996-1998, 2005 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 5)
        Includes photo disc, CD-2114.
      - Law School, 1960s-1970s (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 6)
      - Law School, 1960s-1970s (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 7)
      - Law School, 1987-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 8)
      - Medical College, New York City, 1962-1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 9)
      - Medical College, New York City (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 10)
      - Modern Language, Prof. J. M. Cowan and modern language lab, 1949-1952 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 11)
      - Modern Language and Linguistics, 1989-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 12)
      - Music, 1954-1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 13)
      - Music, 1955-1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 14)
      - Music, 1967-1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 15)
      - Music, 1974-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 16)
      - Music, 1974-1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 17)
      - Music, 1978-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 18)
      - Music, 1988-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 19)
      - Music, 1993-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 20)
      - Music and Theatre, 1966-1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 21)
      - Musical Groups, 1968-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 22)
      - Musical Groups, 1975-1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 23)
      - Musical Groups, 1981-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 24)
      - Nature Study Class, summer session (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 25)
      - Nursery School, 1987-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 26)
      - Orchestra, 1966-1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 27)
      - Orchestra, 1975-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 28)
      - Phi Beta Kappa Key, 1973 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 29)
      - Phi Psi 500, 1977-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 31)
      - Phi Psi 500, 1975-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 30)
      - Recreation, 1975-1980 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 32)
        Students playing frisbee, baseball, kites, pool, etc.
      - ROTC, 1960s-1970s (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 33)
        Students cleaning, practicing drills, classrooms, Captain Kidwell, Major Prahm, Ceremonies in Barton
      - ROTC, 1966-1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 34)
      - ROTC, 1966-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 35)
      - ROTC, 1966-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 35a)
      - ROTC, 1976-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 36)
      - ROTC, 1982-1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 37)
      - ROTC, 1987-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 38)
      - The Savoyards, 1980-1993 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 39)
      - Shakespeare in the Courtyard, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 40)
      - Sherlock Holmes Club, 1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 41)
      - Singing Groups, 1977-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 42)
      - Society of Creative Anachronism, 1987-1991 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 43)
      - Student Activities, 1961-1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 44)
      - Student Activities, 1964-1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 45)
      - Student Activities - Indoors, 1971-1978 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 46)
      - Student Activities - Outdoors, 1969-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 47)
      - Student Activities - Outdoors, 1979 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 48)
      - Student Agencies, 1988-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 49)
      - Student Organizations, 1970-1971 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 50)
      - Summer Activities, 1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 52)
      - Summer College, 1990-1999 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 53)
      - Teaching, 1991-1994 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 54)
      - Textiles and Apparel, 1990-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 55)
      - Theatre Arts, 1960s (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 56)
        One of these folders includes: The Changeling, Theatre de la Renaissance, Balch Courtyard
      - Theatre Arts, 1966-1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 57)
      - Theatre Arts, 1970-1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 58)
      - Theatre Arts, 1975-1986 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 59)
      - Theatre Arts, 1978-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 60)
      - Theatre Arts, 1987-1990 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 61)
      - Theatre Arts, 1992-1997 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 62)
      - Theatre Arts (Historic Photograph) (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 63)
      - Ujamaa Program House, 1972-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 64)
      - Ujamaa Program House, 1988 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 65)
      - Women's Intercollegiate Affairs, 1982 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 66)
      - Women's Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 4-3-15 - 71, Folder 67)
    - People
      - People by category
        - Alumni (Contact Sheets), 1968-1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 1)
        - Alumni - Architecture, Old Boys Renunion, 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 2)
        - Class Officers, 1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 27)
        - Cornell Debaters, Denise Gilbert and Tom McCarthy, 1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 29)
        - Cornell Presidents, 1969-1970 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 31)
        - Four Cornell Presidents, 1977 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 32)
        - Cornell Presidential Councilors, 1975-1981 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 33)
        - Cornell Presidential Councilors, 1984 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 34)
        - Cornell University Council, 1975-1976 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 35)
        - Cornell University Senate, 1970-1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 36)
        - Cranch Report, 1972 (Box 4-3-15 - 72, Folder 53-54)
        - Deans (Box 4-3-15 - 73, Folder 5)
        - Dean's Essay Contest Winner, Jack M. Schrager, 1975 (Box 4-3-15 - 73, Folder 6)
        - Education Policy Committee Students, 1969 (Box 4-3-15 - 73, Folder 15)
        - Employees, 1992-1996 (Box 4-3-15 - 73, Folder 17)
        - Employees, 1996-2000 (Box 4-3-15 - 73, Folder 18)
        - Employees at Work, 1983-1998 (Box 4-3-15 - 73, Folder 19)
        - Employees and Activities, 1970-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 73, Folder 20)
        - Employees and Activities, 1981-1985 (Box 4-3-15 - 73, Folder 21)
        - Employees, Non-Exempt Staff in Action, 1970-1983 (Box 4-3-15 - 74, Folder 46)